

MURTAZA ICECREAMWALA

MURTAZAARIF2K16@GMAIL.COM +918878851524 LINKEDIN | BLOGS

OBJECTIVE

A career in managing software development who can deploy scalable and reliable software solutions at pace and at scale. I focus on customer backward thinking.

SKILLS

5+ years of experience in building software products. Prolific in development using Nodejs, Typescript, Python, Kotlin and Java. My skills include full cycle of product engineering from requirement gathering to post deployment and including software testing and managing people. I have deep experience in developing reusable business workflow and UI presentation layer using Angular. Excellent communication skills, written and verbal

EXPERIENCE

TECH LEAD • SIYA TECH • JULY 2021 - CURRENT

- Created a fantasy sport application for football
- Created a logistics solution like ola.
- Created a Platform as a service for different logistics partner
- Developed a transfer pricing management system
- Developed CRM project with python and sql
- Implemented fully automated pipelines for deployment and testing
- Ensure that company SDLC process is followed by my team member

SOFTWARE ENGINEER I • COMPASS REAL ESTATE • MAY 2020 – JUNE 2021

- To speedup CI/CD pipeline with quality- RAC- Risk
 Assessment of Commit was created which finds out how
 risky the commit is. No other firm other than Microsoft has
 that kind of infrastructure
- Create an automated service which will generate random data for automation testing and training the machine learning algorithm.
- Write data driven integration test in android.
- Build reusable code and libraries for future use

FULL STACK DEVELOPER • SIYA TECH • AUG 2016 - APRIL 2020

- Ensure best practices are followed in SDLC
- Ensure the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs
- Optimize application for maximum speed, cross-platform and scalability
- Experience of code versioning tools, such as Git, Bitbucket, GitHub
- Designing and creating RESTful and GraphQL APIs for internal and partner consumption

• Build an automated scrapper for website using python and nodejs

EDUCATION

B.E. CS • IET DAVV INDORE

CGPA: 8.4

12TH **CBSE** CGPA: 8.5